<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference: Expressions on Aurora User Docs</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-expressions/</link><description>Recent content in Reference: Expressions on Aurora User Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-expressions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Input</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-expressions/input/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-expressions/input/</guid><description>This page lists all the standard evaluatables that are under the &amp;lsquo;Input&amp;rsquo; category.
Away Time number Outputs the amount of time the user has been inactivate. This is determined based on mouse or keyboard interaction.
Away Timer boolean Outputs true if the user has been inactivate for the the amount of time specified. Whether the user is away is determined based on mouse or keyboard interaction.
Key Held boolean Outputs true if the specified keyboard button is currently pressed.</description></item><item><title>Logic</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-expressions/logic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-expressions/logic/</guid><description>This page lists all the standard evaluatables that are under the &amp;lsquo;Logic&amp;rsquo; category.
And boolean Takes two input booleans and outputs true only if both these inputs are also true.
Boolean Change Detector boolean Watches an input boolean evaluatable and outputs true on a frame if the value of the child is different than it was last frame. Otherwise it outputs false.
Can also be configured to only output when the new value of the input is true or the new value is false.</description></item><item><title>Maths</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-expressions/maths/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-expressions/maths/</guid><description>This page lists all the standard evaluatables that are under the &amp;lsquo;Maths&amp;rsquo; category.
Absolute number Takes a number and outputs the absolute (positive) value. E.G. 5 outputs 5 (no change), but -10 would output 10.
Arithmetic Comparison boolean Compares two numbers together and outputs a boolean indicating the result of the comparison. Can choose a comparison from: equal, not equal, less than, less than or equal, greater than, greater than or equal.</description></item><item><title>Misc</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-expressions/misc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-expressions/misc/</guid><description>This page lists all the standard evaluatables that are under the &amp;lsquo;Misc&amp;rsquo; category.
Delay booleannumberstring Takes an input and delays it by the given time period.
Process Running boolean Checks if a process with the given name is currently running.</description></item><item><title>State</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-expressions/state/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-expressions/state/</guid><description>This page lists all the standard evaluatables that are under the &amp;lsquo;State&amp;rsquo; category.
Boolean State Variable boolean Gets a boolean value from the game state.
Enum State Variable boolean Gets a enum value from the game state and compares it to a specified value.
An enum is a discrete set of possible options. For example in Terraria, the biome the player is in is an enum as there are only certain distinct possibilities.</description></item><item><title>String</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-expressions/string/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-expressions/string/</guid><description>This page lists all the standard evaluatables that are under the &amp;lsquo;String&amp;rsquo; category.
String Comparison boolean Compares the values of two strings together. Can compare based on length, alphabetical position, etc. Can be configured to do a case insensitive comparison.
String Constant string Constantly outputs the given string of characters.</description></item></channel></rss>