<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference: Expressions on Aurora User Docs</title><link>//wibble199.github.io/Aurora-Docs/reference-expressions/</link><description>Recent content in Reference: Expressions on Aurora User Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="//wibble199.github.io/Aurora-Docs/reference-expressions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Boolean Expressions</title><link>//wibble199.github.io/Aurora-Docs/reference-expressions/boolean-expressions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//wibble199.github.io/Aurora-Docs/reference-expressions/boolean-expressions/</guid><description>This page lists and explains the types of boolean expressions (sometimes called &amp;lsquo;evaluatables&amp;rsquo;) that you can use to construct your override logic. They are listed in the order they appear in the UI.
Logic Name Description And Requires two other boolean expressions and results in true only when both the sub-expressions are also true. Returns false otherwise. Boolean Constant A constant boolean value.</description></item><item><title>Numeric Expressions</title><link>//wibble199.github.io/Aurora-Docs/reference-expressions/numeric-expressions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//wibble199.github.io/Aurora-Docs/reference-expressions/numeric-expressions/</guid><description>This page lists and explains the types of numeric expressions (sometimes called &amp;lsquo;evaluatables&amp;rsquo;) that you can use to construct your override logic. They are listed in the order they appear in the UI.
State Variable Name Description Numeric State Variable Fetches a numeric state variable from the current application&amp;rsquo;s game state and returns it. Maths Name Description Absolute Takes another numeric expression and returns the positive equivalent of it.</description></item><item><title>String Expressions</title><link>//wibble199.github.io/Aurora-Docs/reference-expressions/string-expressions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//wibble199.github.io/Aurora-Docs/reference-expressions/string-expressions/</guid><description>This page lists and explains the types of string expressions that you can use to construct your override logic. A string is a sequence of zero or more letters/characters etc.
State Variable Name Description String State Variable Gets a string state variable from the current profile&amp;rsquo;s application&amp;rsquo;s game state and returns it. String Name Description String Constant Allows you to type in a string and will always return this value.</description></item></channel></rss>