<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Basic Topics on Aurora User Docs</title><link>//wibble199.github.io/Aurora-Docs/basic-topics/</link><description>Recent content in Basic Topics on Aurora User Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="//wibble199.github.io/Aurora-Docs/basic-topics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Started</title><link>//wibble199.github.io/Aurora-Docs/basic-topics/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//wibble199.github.io/Aurora-Docs/basic-topics/getting-started/</guid><description>When you first open Aurora, you will be presented with a window that looks like the following. Applications On the far left is the application list, with each application shown as an icon. All the applications and games you will see here by default have some sort of integration or preset profile. You are not limited to just these ones however; by scrolling to the bottom of the list and clicking the plus icon you will be able to specify new applications either by selecting from the running process list or by browsing to the exe.</description></item><item><title>Installation</title><link>//wibble199.github.io/Aurora-Docs/basic-topics/installation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//wibble199.github.io/Aurora-Docs/basic-topics/installation/</guid><description>To install Aurora, the easiest way is to download the installer from our GitHub page and simply run it.
After this, you will find Aurora in your start menu. Opening the Aurora program will show you some simple steps you will need to take with detected existing RGB to allow Aurora to take priority when it needs to. It&amp;rsquo;s important you follows these steps otherwise Aurora may not work correctly.</description></item><item><title>User Data</title><link>//wibble199.github.io/Aurora-Docs/basic-topics/user-data/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//wibble199.github.io/Aurora-Docs/basic-topics/user-data/</guid><description>Aurora stores all user data in a directory in the roaming application data folder. This user data includes all your settings (such as preferred devices, bitmap accurracy, etc) as well as all your lighting profiles and recent logs that Aurora has created. You can see the Aurora folder by navigating to %APPDATA%\Aurora in Windows file explorer.
Importing Profiles Profiles that others have made can be imported easily into Aurora using the import button on the &amp;ldquo;Profiles&amp;rdquo; section.</description></item></channel></rss>