<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Devices on Aurora User Docs</title><link>//aurora-rgb.github.io/Docs/devices/</link><description>Recent content in Devices on Aurora User Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="//aurora-rgb.github.io/Docs/devices/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Asus</title><link>//aurora-rgb.github.io/Docs/devices/asus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//aurora-rgb.github.io/Docs/devices/asus/</guid><description>Required Software Asus Aura Sync 1.01.71 - Download The most recent version of Asus Aura Sync, 1.07.79, will NOT work for most users. If you have this version installed, Aurora might either fail to initialize Asus, or even fail to start altogether. Keep reading for instructions on how to downgrade
There is a small chance Aura v1.07.79 works correctly on your system. To force the initialization attempt, you can go to the Device Manager tab in the settings, click the 'View Options' button, and tick the 'Enable unsupported Asus SDK versions' checkbox.</description></item><item><title>Corsair</title><link>//aurora-rgb.github.io/Docs/devices/corsair/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//aurora-rgb.github.io/Docs/devices/corsair/</guid><description>Required Software Corsair iCUE Needed configuration The SDK should come enabled by default when you install iCUE, but in case it doesn&amp;rsquo;t connect, make sure it is enabled.
Known Issues Disabling the desktop profile should cause devices to fallback to their default configuration, however this is bugged for corsair devices specifically, causing them to turn black instead. This bug needs a rework of the aurora implementation to be fixed.</description></item><item><title>Logitech</title><link>//aurora-rgb.github.io/Docs/devices/logitech/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//aurora-rgb.github.io/Docs/devices/logitech/</guid><description>Required Software One of:
Logitech Gaming Software 9.02.65+ Logitech G Hub Needed configuration The SDK should come enabled by default when you install LGS or GHUB, but in case it doesn&amp;rsquo;t connect, make sure it is enabled.
For GHUB:
For LGS:
Open Logitech Gaming Software and go into Settings Enable Game Integration Settings Open the Game Integration Configuration menu Disable Conflicting Settings and Applets Known issues G HUB can take a very long time to fully open and start receiving SDK requests.</description></item><item><title>SteelSeries</title><link>//aurora-rgb.github.io/Docs/devices/steelseries/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//aurora-rgb.github.io/Docs/devices/steelseries/</guid><description>Required Software SteelSeries Engine 3 Needed configuration The SDK should be enabled by default, but in case it&amp;rsquo;s not, make sure the &amp;lsquo;Project Aurora&amp;rsquo; custom application is enabled.
If you still cannot control your keyboard or mouse illumination, check if Color Special Event is enabled in Aurora applet in SSE.
Known Issues Devices with number of zones other than 1, 2 or 12 are not fully supported (ex. Rival 600) - they may still work but not all zones can be controlled.</description></item><item><title>Wooting</title><link>//aurora-rgb.github.io/Docs/devices/wooting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//aurora-rgb.github.io/Docs/devices/wooting/</guid><description>Required Software None. Aurora will connect directly to your keyboard
Needed configuration None. Connection should be automatic. If Aurora fails to connect at first, replug the keyboard and start Aurora again.
Known issues Aurora overrides any lighting profiles on the keyboard. Due to this, it becomes impossible to tell which profile (digital, analog 1-3) is active at any time. There is currently no fix / workaround for this, but this data might be a game state variable in the future.</description></item></channel></rss>