<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Advanced Topics on Aurora User Docs</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/advanced-topics/</link><description>Recent content in Advanced Topics on Aurora User Docs</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/advanced-topics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Animation Editor</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/advanced-topics/animation-editor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/advanced-topics/animation-editor/</guid><description>&lt;p>The &lt;a href="https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/animation/">Animation Layer&lt;/a> allows you to add your own custom animated effects to your peripheral lights. To edit this animation, the Animation Editor used. This is a powerful tool, and fairly easy to use once you understand how it works. As with all unfamiliar things however, it may be daunting at first.&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="concepts-and-definitions">Concepts and Definitions&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Before getting into the guide itself, let me define some of the concepts and features that are required to fully understand how the animations work.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Audio Visualizer Tweaks</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/advanced-topics/visualizer-output/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/advanced-topics/visualizer-output/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Audio Visualizer layer allows you to display a representation of whatever you&amp;rsquo;re listening to on your RGB devices.&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="isolating-applications">Isolating applications&lt;/h1>
&lt;h3 id="why">Why&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>One of the things that annoys me about the layer is that every single sound your computer emits will be shown on the keyboard, which isn&amp;rsquo;t very useful or appealing if you&amp;rsquo;re talking to someone on Discord for example. So I found a way to isolate a single application (in my case, Spotify) in the same audio output as Aurora.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Custom Layout</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/advanced-topics/custom-layout/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/advanced-topics/custom-layout/</guid><description>&lt;p>Intended way to use Aurora with more than keyboard, mouse, mousepad etc. is &lt;em>Remapping&lt;/em> them to CL1-CL5 keys.
This way, they can be integrated with default game effects.&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="creating-custom-layouts">Creating Custom Layouts&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Currently only way to create new layouts is by editing the json files in Aurora&amp;rsquo;s installation folder.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You can save your layouts as &lt;strong>custom_keyboard.json&lt;/strong>, &lt;strong>custom_mouse.json&lt;/strong>,
&lt;strong>custom_mousepad.json&lt;/strong>, &lt;strong>custom_headset.json&lt;/strong> or &lt;strong>custom_chroma.json&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This naming is recommended as you will lose your changes if new layout updates are downloaded&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Overrides System</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/advanced-topics/overrides-system/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/advanced-topics/overrides-system/</guid><description>&lt;p>The overrides system is an an advanced system that allows you to override the properties of layers with other values that are evaluated each frame. This allows for a huge amount of control and customizability with your lighting that layers on their own cannot provide. You can still get fairly customization layers without this system, so do not worry if you don&amp;rsquo;t understand it. This is a feature mainly for advanced users.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>State Variables</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/advanced-topics/state-variables/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/advanced-topics/state-variables/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="what-are-state-variables">What are State Variables?&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>State Variables are numeric, boolean (true/false) or string (sequence of letters) values
that can be obtained and dynamically updated by Aurora as it is running.
Layers such as the Percent Effect Layer or the Animation Layer
can make use of these values to conditionally set the lights on the keyboard.
The values depend on which profile is currently in use,
for example the CSGO profile contains State Variables for health, current ammo, max ammo, etc.
but these specific ones do not work for other profiles such as Minecraft.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>