<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference: Layers on Aurora User Docs</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/</link><description>Recent content in Reference: Layers on Aurora User Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ambilight Layer</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/ambilight/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/ambilight/</guid><description>The ambilight layer takes the average color of the monitor (or specific areas of the monitor) and displays them on the keys.
This can be a very intensive operation and so may not perform well on all machines. You may find that Aurora is lagging or using too much CPU when you use one of these layers.
Properties Name Description Ambilight Effect Type Default - Takes the image from the target and sets the keys to the color at points on that image (see above for an example).</description></item><item><title>Animation Layer</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/animation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/animation/</guid><description>The animation layer is another very powerful but very complex and hard-to-use layer. It allows for you to create custom animations using shapes and by creating key-frames in the animation editor. There is a basic guide on how to create animations here.
This layer can also be triggered when certain events happen. You can select it for when a game-state value changes or when you press/release a key. When in a key-mode, the animation can optionally be translated to the location of the pressed key.</description></item><item><title>Audio Visualizer Layer</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/audio-visualizer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/audio-visualizer/</guid><description>This layer takes in audio data from your computer and visualizes the volume at various frequencies. There are many different customization options for this layer including which frequencies should be detected. Which frequencies are best depends on the type of audio you expect to be playing (rock will be different from classical) but the default frequencies provide a good starting point.
Properties Name Description Equalizer Effect Type Power Bars Waveform Waveform (From bottom) View Type Solid Color - The waveform/bars are displayed in a single color (Primary Color) Alternating Colors - Each bar alternates between Primary and Secondary color.</description></item><item><title>Blinking Layer</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/blinking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/blinking/</guid><description>The blinking layer sets the colors of the specified keys to flash between two alternatives, with no fading between the colors. Like to the breathing layer, it allows either or both of these colors to be randomized if you wish.
Properties Name Description Primary Color The solid color to set all the affected keys to during the first phase. Use Random Primary Tick this to use a random color during first phase instead of Primary Color.</description></item><item><title>Breathing Layer</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/breathing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/breathing/</guid><description>The breathing layer fades the colors of the specified keys between two colors. In that regard it is similar to the Gradient Fill Layer, however this layer also allows the colors to be randomized, so that the keyboard fades between unpredictable colors.
Properties Name Description Primary Color The solid color to set all the affected keys to during the first phase. Use Random Primary Tick this to use a random color during first phase instead of Primary Color.</description></item><item><title>Conditional &amp; Comparison Layers</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/conditional-comparisons/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/conditional-comparisons/</guid><description>These layers are no longer necessary and the Overrides System should be used instead as it has more functionality than these layers. They will remain in Aurora so as not to break existing profiles.
Conditional Layer The conditional layer sets the color of the given keys to one of two colors, based on whether the a boolean value (a yes/no) from the game or system or is true or false. Not all games have boolean properties available.</description></item><item><title>Glitch Effect Layer</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/glitch-effect/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/glitch-effect/</guid><description>The glitch layer simply randomizes each key’s color every time it updates. The frequency of the update is configurable.
Properties Name Description Update Interval The time in seconds between the key&amp;rsquo;s randomization. Allow Transparency If true, the random color may be transparent.</description></item><item><title>Gradient Fill Layer</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/gradient-fill/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/gradient-fill/</guid><description>This layer sets all the specified keys to the same color, determined by the gradient. Unlike the regular gradient layer, all keys are the same color. You can think of the gradient as being a “timeline”, and the colors of all the keys are set based on how far through the timeline we are. This can be used to create a fade effect between multiple different colors.
Properties Name Description Gradient The gradient that will be used to set the keys&amp;rsquo; color to.</description></item><item><title>Gradient Layer</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/gradient/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/gradient/</guid><description>The Gradient Layer shows a gradient effect on the specified keys. The gradient can also be animated to move across the keyboard to give a wave effect. If it helps to understand how it works, you can imagine the gradient to be displayed on a (possibly moving) rectangle, and each key acts as a “window” onto that rectangle.
Properties Name Description Gradient The solid color to set all the affected keys to.</description></item><item><title>Image Layer</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/image/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/image/</guid><description>The image layer takes an image saved on your computer and attempts to replicate it on the keyboard by averaging the nearby color at different points. Obviously one should not expect to get the same fidelity you would get with a high-res image, but some images can provide nice effects. In addition, Aurora supports the use of animated GIF images.
Properties Name Description Selected Image The file path to the image you wish to display.</description></item><item><title>Interactive Layer</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/interactive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/interactive/</guid><description>The interactive layer listens for key presses on the keyboard and plays an animation from that key. This can be used to make ripple effects (as shown in the GIF below) or have the key light up and slowly fade out when it’s been pressed.
Properties Name Description Interactive Effect Type Key Wave - A circle emerges from the pressed key and slowly expands. It is initially Primary Color, then fades to Secondary Color.</description></item><item><title>Lock Color Layer</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/lock-color/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/lock-color/</guid><description>The lock layer allows you to have keys light up (or pulse) in a color when one of the “lock” keys is active (caps lock, num lock or scroll lock). You can use this to make a warning for when caps lock is on for example, or perhaps turn off the lights on the numpad when the numpad is off.
This layer functionality can be incorporated using the Overrides System. That said, it is simpler to use this layer for the pulse feature than to use the Override System alternative.</description></item><item><title>Particle (Interactive) Layer</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/particle-interactive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/particle-interactive/</guid><description>This layer is very similar to the regular particle layer, however instead of constantly spawning particle it does so for each pressed key. If set to region mode, the region will automatically be changed to be the keys that are pressed which allows for effects emanating from where you press.
Properties See particle layer properties.</description></item><item><title>Particle Layer</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/particle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/particle/</guid><description>The particle layer spawns a number of particles which can independently move (based on the layer&amp;rsquo;s settings) and have a color. After a specified amount of time, the particles are removed from the canvas.
Some examples of what can be done with this layer are shown below (both are available as presets), but this is by no means all that can be achieved. Experiment with it!
There is no limit on the number of particles that can be spawned at once.</description></item><item><title>Percent (Gradient) Effect Layer</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/percent-gradient-effect/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/percent-gradient-effect/</guid><description>This layer is very similar to the Percent Effect Layer, but makes use of a gradient instead of a progress/background color. This layer does not have a background.
Properties Name Description Current Value The path of a State Variable or a number. This value represents the current value of whichever variable you are watching, e.g. health, ammo, etc. Maximum Value The path of a State Variable or a number. This value represents the value that is the maximum value of the percent layer.</description></item><item><title>Percent Effect Layer</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/percent-effect/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/percent-effect/</guid><description>The percent effect layer allows you to have the color of some set keys dependent on a numeric variable that can be provided by the computer (such as how much RAM or CPU is in use) or by the game if it is supported (e.g. health in CS:GO or speed in Euro Truck Sim).
Properties Name Description Current Value The path of a State Variable or a number. This value represents the current value of whichever variable you are watching, e.</description></item><item><title>Radial Layer</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/radial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/radial/</guid><description>A layer that provides a gradient that rotates around a single point and optionally spins.
Note that this gradient is generated using discrete pie-shaped segments of colour. This color is determined by the median color at a particular point on the gradient. For example, if there were 4 segments, each would have a 90 degree arc. The first would use the color at 45 degrees (90 / 2) the second at 135 degrees, etc.</description></item><item><title>Script Layer</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/script/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/script/</guid><description>The script layer on its own will do nothing, however it is one of the most powerful, advanced layers. It provides an interface for users to create custom effects using the Aurora API in either C# or Python. More details can be found on the project&amp;rsquo;s Old-Wiki and example scripts can be found in the Script Examples folder on GitHub. The limits of what this layer can do really are up to you.</description></item><item><title>Shortcut Assistant Layer</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/shortcut-assistant/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/shortcut-assistant/</guid><description>The Shortcut Assistant layer shows possible key presses when a modifier key is pressed. The defined shortcuts will set the keyboard lights when they are partially pressed. For example, if you had a shortcut defined for Ctrl + C and Ctrl + V, whenever you press control, the other layers below are dimmed and the C and V letter light up in whichever color is specified.
Properties Name Description Dim Background If this is checked, when Aurora detects you a pressing a modifier key (Ctrl, Shift, Alt) then it will display Dimming Color over all keys before rendering the shortcut keys.</description></item><item><title>Solid Color Layer</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/solid-color/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/solid-color/</guid><description>The Solid Color Layer is for setting static colors for specific keys. The keys will constantly be lit in the given color (providing they aren’t overridden by a higher-up layer). This is one of the most simple layers in Aurora, but can be useful for things such as highlighting controls such as WASD in video games.
If you want to set the color of the entire (or most) of the keyboard, consider using the Solid Fill Color Layer instead.</description></item><item><title>Solid Fill Color Layer</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/solid-fill-color/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/solid-fill-color/</guid><description>Similar to the Solid Color layer, however it does not have fine control over which keys are lit and so fills the entire canvas (keyboard, mouse and any other peripherals) with the given color. This layer is useful for setting static backgrounds, saving you from having to manually add each key.
Properties Name Description Color The solid color to set all the affected keys to.</description></item><item><title>Timer Key Layer</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/timer-key/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/timer-key/</guid><description>The timer layer waits for one or more keys to be pressed (do not have to be the keys displaying the lights) and sets the color of the keys to be something else for a set duration, after which they return to their original color. This layer can be used for things such as ability timers for games that have no game state integration.
Properties Name Description Default Color The color that the keys are by default and when the timer is not active.</description></item><item><title>Toggle Key Layer</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/toggle-key/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/toggle-key/</guid><description>The toggle key layer allows for the turning on or off some lights based on the key press of another specific key. This layer can be useful for things such as indicators for whether something is toggled on/off in a game.
If you are using caps lock, num lock or scroll lock as a trigger key it is probably better to use the Lock Layer to ensure the key light state stays synced with the lock state properly.</description></item><item><title>Toolbar Layer</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/toolbar/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/toolbar/</guid><description>The toolbar layer is a layer that shows one key as “active” and all others assigned to it as “inactive”. When a different key is pressed, the pressed key becomes the active one instead. This works similarly to how toolbars/item bars work in video games such as Factorio or Minecraft.
The layer can also be toggled to listen for the scroll wheel to allow scrolling through the toolbar by turning on the Enable Scroll configuration option.</description></item><item><title>Wrapper Lights Layer (LightFX)</title><link>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/wrapper/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.project-aurora.com/Docs/reference-layers/wrapper/</guid><description>The wrapper layer is a special layer that is able to display lighting received from games that have been patched with the relevant wrapper patch and that have native lighting of some sort.
To patch a game, navigate to &amp;ldquo;Settings&amp;rdquo; -&amp;gt; &amp;ldquo;Devices &amp;amp; Wrappers&amp;rdquo; -&amp;gt; &amp;ldquo;Install Wrapper Patch for xxx&amp;rdquo;, where xxx is the name of the native lighting provided by that game. Do not patch the game with their own device&amp;rsquo;s brand (unless that is also the provider of the in game lighting).</description></item></channel></rss>